<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>music on @bluepulsar971</title>
    <link>https://losangeles971.github.io/bluepulsar971/tags/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in music on @bluepulsar971</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://losangeles971.github.io/bluepulsar971/tags/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Molly</title>
      <link>https://losangeles971.github.io/bluepulsar971/music/molly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://losangeles971.github.io/bluepulsar971/music/molly/</guid>
      <description>Song Author     The House of the Rising Sun The Animals   The Sound of Silence Simon &amp;amp; Garfunkel   White Rabbit Jefferson Airplane   Hotel California Eagles   Perfect Day Lou Reed   Paranoid Android Radiohead   Comfortably Numb Pink Floyd   Stairway to Heaven Led Zeppelin   People Are Strange The Doors   Eight Miles High The Byrds   White Room Cream   Glory Box Portishead   The Great Gig In The Sky Pink Floyd   Runaway Train Soul Asylum   Life on Mars?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oddity</title>
      <link>https://losangeles971.github.io/bluepulsar971/music/oddity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://losangeles971.github.io/bluepulsar971/music/oddity/</guid>
      <description>Song Author     Mother Pink Floyd   Space Oddity David Bowie   The Man Who Sold The World David Bowie   Comfortably Numb Pink Floyd   Paranoid Android Radiohead   Glory Box Portishead   No Surprises Radiohead   Starman David Bowie   People Are Strange The Doors   Life on Mars? David Bowie   About Her Malcolm McLaren   Until The End Of The World U2   October U2   Killer Shangri-Lah (Killing Eve OST) Pshycotic Beats   The Crying Game Boy George   Karma Police Radiohead   Heroes David Bowie   Creep Radiohead   American Pie Don McLean   A Horse with No Name America   God Knows (You Gotta Give to Get) El Perro Del Mar   Shine On You Crazy Diamond (Pt.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
